<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Portfolio of Bryan Miguel – Advertising Copywriter]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Portfolio of Bryan Miguel – Advertising Copywriter]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 23:07:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Summerfest - Campaign]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Summerfest - Campaign</h1><p>Smile Louder.Every year, nearly 1,000,000 people come to Summerfest to watch 800 bands jam out on 11 stages through 2 straight weeks. This red smiley-logoed music festival is the Guinness Book of World Records' biggest music festival. But surprisingly, the world's biggest music festival isn't all that well known outside of Wisconsin. So we helped them with a campaign to attract more eyes and ears.Advertising and branding outside of the cheese state was already at a minimum. So to help make the brand more recognizable, we built the campaign around the logo.  </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8b3c117e-1b07-48ea-be86-e8495616be64.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/summerfest-campaign/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c0e24b56-f097-455e-896d-edc1e1aed6c7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 23:07:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[There are two types of people in this world.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>There are two types of people in this world.</h1><p>Yes – I know – there are way more than two. Just bare with me.There are heroes. And then there are people who aren’t so much.A hero is exactly how you imagine them. Suave. Skilled. Talented. Flawless. They’re Pierce Brosnan as James Bonds –even if he’s holding the gun wrong, it’s a guaranteed headshot.Your less-thans are placed in the same scenario, but without the necessary skills to succeed – but they're never without hope. That means, even if the odds are completely stacked against them, they still try. That’s Seth Rogan inThe Interviewand Reese Witherspoon inLegally Blonde. These less-thans are no hero – they’re human.I bring this up because I’m not a hero. There was a point where I really tried to be. I read and wrote books about advertising, attended portfolio school, took on unpaid internships, attended conferences, listened to speakers, grew my network, found a mentor and worked my ass off. But honestly, I can’t say for certain that any of those things have helped me get any closer to becoming a David Droga or Alex Bogusky.I don’t know everything about a particular demographic. I can’t say that I have an engineer’s knowledge about a product. And I saw Paul BlartMall Copin theaters and didn’t walk out.But remember. Somehow these less-thans were able to overcome these obstacles. And without the necessary skills, they had to approach problems creatively.I’m a city boy who sold tractors to farmers. I’m an apartment renter selling termite protection to homeowners. I'm an ex-Northwetern Mutual life insurance salesman – who decided that I hated the business and never wanted to work in life insurance again – who eventually took on a life insurance agency as a client and still did great work.I can’t guarantee that everything I touch turns to gold. But I can promise you that I’ll try to solve the problem creatively. I mean, I’m only human.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/there-are-two-types-of-people-in-this-world/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">426e23c7-29ea-4884-8201-e7aa1c8e891f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 22:37:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zoetis Honoring Caregivers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Zoetis Honoring Caregivers</h1><p>Honoring Caregivers is an award that praises the under-appreciated work of pig caregivers. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/37db9314-ac39-4266-aee8-cea1c24f18be.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/zoetis-honoring-caregivers/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b7fb4142-2cb2-40da-87ff-44dda27e9686</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 22:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>