<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Portfolio of Bryan Miguel – Advertising Copywriter]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Portfolio of Bryan Miguel – Advertising Copywriter]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 22:48:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zoetis Honoring Caregivers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Zoetis Honoring Caregivers</h1><p>Honoring Caregivers was an award that praised the under-appreciated work of pig caregivers. Caregivers are given the greatest responsibility of overseeing the health and care of a pig's life. They're the ones who assist with the piglet as its born, ensure they remain healthy throughout their life and treat the pig with a high degree of dignity and respect. This award was originally an effort of Pfizer Animal health. But when Zoetis became a separate entity, they took the program with them. Though this was a successful program when it first started, Honoring Caregivers hasn't run since 2010. In 2014, Kevin Sparrow (Art Director) and I were asked to blow off the dust and breathe new life to the award.We had a very minimal budget to get this up and running. We knew money was already set aside for the cash prize, flying the winners to New York City and filming the winners to create a short documentary. With what remained, we were tasked with creating a campaign that included print ads, brochures, web banners, tradeshow graphics and a website. So creatively, all we really had the money for was a single image and a logo. Whatever we did, we knew we had to make sure the campaign's elements would translate well from an iPhone screen to a billboard. But if this program was a success, we would have the ability to expand the campaign's universe the next year.Even though Honoring Caregivers was the name of the Pfizer program, we had to make sure that Pork Operation Owners and Caregivers knew that this was a big deal. We needed to let them know that this was prestigious – especially since there were no other major awards for animal caregivers. So we took inspiration from other award shows to create the Academy Awards for Pig Caregivers.The program was a hit. We received thousands of nominations for well-deserved caregivers. We earned a lot of traction from all the major national pork publications and many local media. And Zoetis was at the center of it all. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/37db9314-ac39-4266-aee8-cea1c24f18be.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/zoetis-honoring-caregivers/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b7fb4142-2cb2-40da-87ff-44dda27e9686</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 22:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Started on The Grid]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Getting Started on The Grid</h1><p>Click the pencil icon in the bottom left to read more...</p><img src="https://d33v4339jhl8k0.cloudfront.net/docs/assets/54dd53ebe4b086c0c0966e7a/images/5616ac809033602f2d9baebd/file-t8c0VXJ6mq.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bryanmiguel/getting-started-on-the-grid/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a82f953-3bc5-4bf4-8b41-b5b785110f3a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 21:58:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>